

SUMMARY

Innovative and harmonious Software Engineer with more than 2 years of experience in various roles. Have many different skills in areas like Front-End Development, Back-End Development, Data Analysis and Artificial Intelligence. Seeking a future career in Full-Stack Development roles and want to develop skills in Web Development and Computer Communications areas.

EDUCATION

ISTANBUL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

2017-2022

B.Sc in Computer Engineering

•Graduation project: "An IoT Network Design Proposal in Smart Campuses for Anomaly Detection"

EXPERIENCE ___

DERIVCO SPORTS

February 2023 - Ongoing

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- Worked on Serverless and RESTful backend projects with DotNet on Azure.
- · Helped improve the dashboard and admin panel for content administrators using React.
- Took part in developing and maintaining company's US data streams which is actively carrying millions of users' data each day.
- Pioneered more streamlined processes of CI/CD with Infrastructure as Code using Terraform and YAML to enable the company to enter and maintain different market infrastructures in Azure and Azure DevOps.
- I have sucessfully got AZ-900 Certficate for MS Azure

DEFIA SOFTWARE

January 2022 - June 2022

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- Designed, developed and refactored RESTful and RESTless APIs, Front-End Applications and Cross-Platform applications.
- Developed end-to-end testing for implemented software.
- Used Java, C#, C++, JavaScript and python in projects.
- Developed an Translation App to be used in meetings with clients, whom can not speak English or Turkish, using QT, OpenCV and Azure Cognitive Services.

VESTEL ELECTRONICS IOT - BIG DATA AND AI

August 2020 - January 2022

PART-TIME SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- · Worked on transmitting or managing data from millions of Vestel Products with Python and Go.
- Implemented Google Cloud Platform infrastructure to store and manage the data.
- Visualised and Analysed the data for ML projects or Business needs.
- Built ML projects with the data such as: predictive maintenance, recommendation AI and customer segmentation.
- Developed an Desktop-App with Electron for developers to manage Terraform more efficiently via a GUI.

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES Java | Python | JavaScript | Go | C# | C++

FRAMEWORKS React & React.Native | ASP.NET Core | Spring Boot | Node.js | Flask | Gin Framework

TECHNOLOGIES Kafka | GCP | Docker | PostgreSQL | MySQL | Couchbase | MongoDB

COMPUTER SCIENCE Data Structures | Algorithms | OOP | Design Patterns | Data Analysis | Artificial Intelligence

LANGUAGES Native: Turkish Fluent: English Beginner: Spanish

2017-2022